MIKE SKALANDUNAS

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+1 (203) 548 - 1521 mskalandunas@gmail.com mikeskalandunas.com

- (n) /mskalandunas
- (a) @mskalandunas
- in in/mskalandunas
- mosaicmusic.io

SUMMARY

Full stack JavaScript developer with an extensive background in game audio & audio implementation. I pride myself on being a quick and active learner who loves picking up new stacks and technologies. Building high quality tools and user experiences is my passion.

EDUCATION

2016 CODE FELLOWS

Advanced Software Development in Full Stack JavaScript

2008 - 2011 BERKLEE COLLEGE OF MUSIC

Bachelor of Arts in Film & Game Scoring

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2016 LEARNBIG

Developed, implemented, & tested a web-based eLearning platform using a proprietary JavaScript framework along with Node.js and a variety of open source modules. I also worked closely with post-production, content, and design teams to ensure that all of their goals were being realized and represented as intended.

2012 - PRESENT MOSAIC MUSIC

Freelance music composition, sound design, & tooling.

2011 - 2012 FBP SOUND

Developed a sample library using odd instruments. Tasks including sampling, sound design, synthesis, KSP scripting, and tooling in Max/MSP.

SKILLS

WEB DEVELOPMENT

JavaScript (ES5 + 6), React, Angular, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Node.js, Express, Koa, MongoDB, Mocha, Chai, Gulp, & Webpack

OTHER

Azure, Agile methodologies, & Git